Just added to your cart
-----------------------

Qty:

Continue shopping

Submit

Close search

[

](https://thefalloffera.com/)

Search [Account](https://thefalloffera.com/account/login)[ Shopping Cart

0 items](https://thefalloffera.com/cart)

Privacy policy
==============

Privacy Policy

\-----

This Privacy Policy describes how your personal information is collected, used, and shared when you visit or make a purchase from jcoleshop.myshopify.com (the “Site”).

PERSONAL INFORMATION WE COLLECT  
When you visit the Site, we automatically collect certain information about your device, including information about your web browser, IP address, time zone, and some of the cookies that are installed on your device. Additionally, as you browse the Site, we collect information about the individual web pages or products that you view, what websites or search terms referred you to the Site, and information about how you interact with the Site. We refer to this automatically-collected information as “Device Information”.

We collect Device Information using the following technologies:  
\- “Cookies” are data files that are placed on your device or computer and often include an anonymous unique identifier. For more information about cookies, and how to disable cookies, visit http://www.allaboutcookies.org.  
\- “Log files” track actions occurring on the Site, and collect data including your IP address, browser type, Internet service provider, referring/exit pages, and date/time stamps.  
\- “Web beacons”, “tags”, and “pixels” are electronic files used to record information about how you browse the Site.

Additionally when you make a purchase or attempt to make a purchase through the Site, we collect certain information from you, including your name, billing address, shipping address, payment information (including credit card numbers, third party payment accounts such as PayPal), email address, IP address, and phone number. We refer to this information as “Order Information”.

When we talk about “Personal Information” in this Privacy Policy, we are talking both about Device Information and Order Information.

HOW DO WE USE YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION?  
We use the Order Information that we collect generally to fulfill any orders placed through the Site (including processing your payment information, arranging for shipping, and providing you with invoices and/or order confirmations). Additionally, we use this Order Information to:  
\- Communicate with you;  
\- Screen our orders for potential risk or fraud; and  
\- When in line with the preferences you have shared with us, provide you with information or advertising relating to our products or services.

We use the Device Information that we collect to help us screen for potential risk and fraud (in particular, your IP address), and more generally to improve and optimize our Site (for example, by generating analytics about how our customers browse and interact with the Site, and to assess the success of our marketing and advertising campaigns).

Marketing and advertising campaigns will be developed for broader audiences based on the Device Information and Order Information collected.

SHARING YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION  
We share your Personal Information with third parties to help us use your Personal Information, as described above. For example, we use Shopify to power our online store--you can read more about how Shopify uses your Personal Information here: https://www.shopify.com/legal/privacy. We also use Google Analytics to help us understand how our customers use the Site -- you can read more about how Google uses your Personal Information here: https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/. You can also opt-out of Google Analytics here: https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout.

Finally, we may also share your Personal Information to comply with applicable laws and regulations, to respond to a subpoena, search warrant or other lawful request for information we receive, or to otherwise protect our rights.

BEHAVIORAL ADVERTISING  
As described above, we use your Personal Information to provide you with targeted advertisements or marketing communications we believe may be of interest to you. For more information about how targeted advertising works, you can visit the Network Advertising Initiative’s (“NAI”) educational page at http://www.networkadvertising.org/understanding-online-advertising/how-does-it-work.

You can opt out of targeted advertising by using the links below:  
\- Facebook and Instagram: https://www.facebook.com/settings/?tab=ads  
\- Google: https://www.google.com/settings/ads/anonymous  
\- Bing: https://advertise.bingads.microsoft.com/en-us/resources/policies/personalized-ads

Additionally, you can opt out of some of these services by visiting the Digital Advertising Alliance’s opt-out portal at: http://optout.aboutads.info/.

DO NOT TRACK  
Please note that we do not alter our Site’s data collection and use practices when we see a Do Not Track signal from your browser.

YOUR RIGHTS  
If you are a European resident, you have the right to access personal information we hold about you and to ask that your personal information be corrected, updated, or deleted. If you would like to exercise this right, please contact us through the contact information below.

Additionally, if you are a European resident we note that we are processing your information in order to fulfill contracts we might have with you (for example if you make an order through the Site), or otherwise to pursue our legitimate business interests listed above. Additionally, please note that your information will be transferred outside of Europe, including to Canada and the United States.

DATA RETENTION  
When you place an order through the Site, we will maintain your Order Information for our records unless and until you ask us to delete this information.

CHANGES  
We may update this privacy policy from time to time in order to reflect, for example, changes to our practices or for other operational, legal or regulatory reasons.

CONTACT US  
For more information about our privacy practices, if you have questions, or if you would like to make a complaint, please contact us by e-mail at weborders@somethinginked.com or by mail using the details provided below:

J Cole Official Shop  
\[Re: Privacy Compliance Officer\]  
1018 Elm Hill Pike, Nashville, TN, 37210

\-----

By placing an order on the Site, you consent to the terms of this privacy policy.

#### Contact  
Information

Email Address

#### Feedback

We're listening. How can we help you today?

* * *

2021 © Dreamer Inc. / Site Design & Development by [Eflat Inc.](https://www.eflatinc.com/)

Country/region
--------------

United States (USD $)

Find Us on Social Networks

Use left/right arrows to navigate the slideshow or swipe left/right if using a mobile device

* Choosing a selection results in a full page refresh.
* Press the space key then arrow keys to make a selection.
